[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "What is your reaction to what has happened here with your longtime friend James DiMaggio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Obviously, it's been a tragedy from the beginning for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James DiMaggio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "You, Berry and James DiMaggio have gone on regular camping trips together, is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "That's correct, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Berry", "James DiMaggio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "What kind of man is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Do you think there is credence to that family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "You know, there is always a possibility of something.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Just to clarify -- just to clarify, you mean Hannah, not Megan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I'm sorry, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Any upheaval with a partner or with a business or anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "PANSWICK: You know, if anything, his life, I believe, was getting simpler.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What is her state of mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "She really believes that she's not getting a fair shake and that Jim especially isn't getting a share shake, that, you know, everybody is very upset and it's tragic what's happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Was he seeing anybody currently that you are aware of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Not that I know of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Berry"], "PERSON": ["Smokey"]}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Right, and Berry, obviously, again, Smokey Robinson's son, do you know if Smokey is aware of this connection and what has happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Berry -- Smokey is not really -- I mean, I think Smokey is probably twice, probably once at Berry's wedding and maybe one other time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Berry", "Smokey Robinson", "Smokey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Was he somebody that had any kind of military training or training with explosives or access to this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "You know, there is a couple things that I find interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "There was no problem there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I would say beyond that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What would you say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, if that were the case -- I mean, I don't necessarily know if that's the case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, he's certainly hoping it isn't his friend and we live in such a litigious society, Piers, that probably you and I both should say that this man is accused of kidnapping this girl and murdering her mother and probably her brother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Is there anything inherently wrong anyway in networks running documentaries or drama series on big political figures of the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "ICH: No, and they do it all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Do you think that she can win, or has her time come and gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I have no idea whether she'll run or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "What if it was Chris Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I think --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Do you think he can actually win the general election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Is there a chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "But look, this is a serious job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", ":"], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Is he the most shameless politician in American history?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "Well, that's --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Does it really matter the forum he chooses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "You know, is there a -- is there an opportunity there for people to make a stand, perhaps even consider a boycott and say no, you're not going to behave in this Dickensian (ph) way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "EX", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "And in terms of Edward Snowden, what -- what is your overview where we are with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "In limbo and at least we're out of that hotel.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What is served here this (ph) fast (ph) and particularly, if he's about to start grilling some of his victims?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "You know, it is a farce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Oh, I'm doing great, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Are you basically signaling that you're back in the race again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "What I'm -- what I'm signaling is that I -- yes, I think it's a very important time in our country's history and particularly, and as I talked about here tonight within the Republican Party, and you know, we see a lot of debate and division there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "You must know Iowa pretty well because I think from memory, you went to them like 350 different parts of it, didn't you, in the last Republican Nominee race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Yes, we did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "The gap between the rich and poor in America, is it -- is it still the economy driving most people's concern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJS", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Yes, I -- I think it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Can we expect to see you and Reince Priebus bouncing back on the airwave saying what a great idea it was after all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, I guess the whole point is, you know, what makes Hillary Clinton such a unique individual that she would be treated barely differently than any other politician I can think of.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Are you comfortable with that one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, I don't know how comfortable I'd be on (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bella"]}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Well, I -- I -- I announced some exciting news -- personal news that we're actually doing a small audition to our -- our house because we have to put an elevator in and handicapped bathroom and bedroom because Bella is going strong and doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Tell me what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, just like you said, I was spear-fishing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Did you think that you -- you had it -- it was like, kill or you how were you feeling at that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "You know, I'll -- I'll tell you, to be honest with you, I believe with all my heart that God sustained me in that moment of time to give me no fear and no worry, no anxiety.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What is it with you and monkeys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Or is he picking you out for special attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I think that he's -- he's continually challenging me to trust him, which is what I believe that we all need to do through hard times, through good times, through bad times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Why do you think monkeys dislike him so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Well, one time was kind of my fault actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "Is that -- is that what I'm hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "More or less.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "How are you feeling about it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "It's still a lot to take in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "Are you going to be back to normal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "I mean, if the good lord is watching tonight, and I'm sure he is, would you like him just to lay off you a bit for a while?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130808pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "And playing the lottery?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "No, I don't play the lottery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]